bitesizebio.com 2016-11-22

# Privacy Policy - Bitesize Bio

(Last Updated: December 15, 2014)

At BitesizeBio (“BSB,” “we,” or “us”), we are committed to ensuring the privacy of our customers. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes how personal information is collected from users of the BitesizeBio website at www.bitesizebio.com (the “Site”), and how that information is used and disclosed. By using our Site, you consent to the terms of this Policy.

We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time and will notify you of such changes by posting the modified Policy on our Site and indicating at the top of the Policy document the date it was last updated. Your use of the Site following the posting of such changes shall constitute your consent to any changes to BitesizeBio’s privacy practices.

### WHAT IS PERSONAL INFORMATION?

**Personal Information** :

Personal information is information that specifically identifies an individual, such as an individual’s name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card (or other account number) when directly linked to him or her, such as information about his or her purchases. Personal information also includes demographic information, such as date of birth, gender, geographic area and preferences when such information is linked to other personal information that identifies an individual.

**Aggregate Information** :

Personal information does not include “aggregate” information. Aggregate information is data collected about a group or category of products, services or customers from which individual customer identities have been removed. In other words, information about how you use a service may be collected and combined with information about how others use the same service, but no personal information will be included in the resulting data. Likewise, information about the products you purchase may be collected and combined with information about the products purchased by others. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and customer needs so that we can better consider new products and services, and tailor existing products and services (including the Site) to customer desires.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

You provide personal information to us in a number of ways when you visit the Site.

For example, you provide us with personal information when you:

  * Create an account and subscribe to our e-mail newsletter or other  
services (“Services”)
  * Conduct a transaction through the Site
  * Participate in a survey, contest, or other promotion on the Site
  * Contact us by e-mail for any reason, such as to request help with  
the Services, or to provide us with your comments/feedback
  * Submit personal information in connection with photos/stories for  
potential use and/or publication on the Site

We may collect your name, image, billing and shipping addresses, e-mail address, phone number, credit card number and expiration date in this manner. We may also collect certain demographic information in connection with your participation in any survey, contest, sweepstakes, or promotion on the Site. You understand that when you submit information to us, including but not limited to comments, stories, photos, or videos (“Content”), for participation in any survey, contest, sweepstakes, or promotion offered on the Site, that BitesizeBio may post or publish this information on the Site, and that you also agree BitesizeBio has an unlimited right to use your Content. Your participation in such surveys, contests, sweepstakes, or promotions offered on the Site, and associated information sharing, is done at your own risk – Please keep this in mind.

Important Note: You have the option of telling us how you wish to be identified in connection with your photos, stories, comments and elsewhere on the Site. If you choose to use your real name (or include any personally identifying information as part of your “nickname”) that information will be publicly displayed on our Site where noted. Therefore, please use caution in determining how you wish to be identified on the Site.

Additionally, when you visit our Site, some information is automatically collected, such as your computer’s operating system and browser type, version, and capabilities (such as whether JavaScript is enabled and cookies are accepted), your Internet Protocol (IP) address and the time and date of your visit, the referring site (if applicable), as well as screen resolution, color and depth. This information is tracked through the use of web beacons and logs.

**Cookies** : Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer by your browser at the request of a web site to store your personal preferences. BitesizeBio may use cookies and your internet protocol (IP) address for certain functions to better your online experience.

**Web Beacons** : “Web beacons” (also known as “web bugs,” “action tags,” “pixel trackers,” or “clear GIFs”) may also be used on the Site or in e-mails relating to the Site. Web beacons are small graphic images placed on a webpage, web-based document, or in an e-mail message that allow the collection of certain information and monitor user activity on the Site. Web beacons are invisible because of their size (only 1 by 1 pixel) and because they are the same color as the background of the web page.

We do not use Web beacons to collect personal information about you. Web beacons are used to collect non-personal information such as the IP address of the computer that the Web beacon is sent to, the URL of the page the Web user comes from and the time the Web beacon is activated (such as when you view the webpage, advertisement, or e-mail that contains the Web beacon).

We use cookies on this site. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer by websites to offer a personalised service and improve the site. Cookies are widely used. By continuing to use this site, you are consenting to our use of cookies. [More – Cookie Policy](http://bitesizebio.com/cookie-policy)

### HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION

We are able to offer the Services to you, in part, based on your willingness to be reached by our third-party advertisers. Your Personal Information (other than Sensitive Information) will be shared with advertisers on an aggregate and non-aggregate basis. We also use contact information from your Personal Information to send you information about the Services, our other offerings and to keep you informed of our other products and services that may be of interest to you and to contact you about your billing account status.

Please keep in mind, though, that we do not control, and are not responsible for, the practices of our third-party advertisers. If you wish to stop receiving future communications from us and/or third party advertisers, or if you wish to prevent the transfer and/or sale of your Personal Information to third parties (subject to restrictions contained in applicable regional and national law), please see the Removal of Your Information/Opting Out section below.

By submitting your Personal Information at the Site, you agree to receive e-mail marketing from us and our third-party advertisers. In addition, where you submit a telephone number at the Site, if ever, you agree that such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application for purposes of providing customer support where appropriate.

We reserve the right to release current or past Personal Information: (i) in the event that we believe that the Site and/or the Services is/are being or has/have been used in violation of this Privacy Policy, the [Terms of Use](http://bitesizebio.com/terms-of-use/) or to commit unlawful acts; (ii) if the information is subpoenaed or otherwise requested pursuant to a valid legal proceeding; or (iii) if we are sold or acquired. Moreover, you hereby consent to the disclosure of any record or communication to any third-party when we, in our sole discretion, determine the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with third-parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time.

If you enroll in certain Member programs, we may use your Personal Information to send you a welcome email that may confirm your user name and password. In addition, we may send you electronic newsletters, contact you about Services and other products, services, information and news that may be of interest to you, and provide you with targeted feedback. In addition, if you identify yourself to us by sending us an email with questions or comments, we may use such information (including Personal Information) to respond to your questions or comments, and we may file your questions or comments for future reference.

We may also supplement the information that we collect with information from other sources to assist us in evaluating and improving the Site and Services, and to determine your preferences so that we can tailor the Site and Services to your needs.

### SHARING PERSONAL INFORMATION

We do not sell, trade, or rent personal information to third parties without your prior consent except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy. We may share personal information with third-party vendors who assist us in performing internal functions necessary to operate our business. These functions may include, for example, analyzing traffic information or other data, providing marketing assistance to us, mailing items, processing credit card transactions, and fulfilling or delivering orders. In all cases we limit the information shared with our third-party vendors to that which is necessary to carry out those functions. We are not responsible for any additional information you provide to these parties, and we encourage you to become familiar with their practices before disclosing information directly to them.

We also disclose personal information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a subpoena, warrant or court order) or with requests of law enforcement authorities, or other similar inquiries; to enforce or apply this Policy or our other policies or agreements; to initiate, render, bill and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our or our customers’ rights, property or safety; to protect our customers from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of our Site; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay.

In addition, information about our customers, including personally identifiable information, may be disclosed or transferred as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing or sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personally identifiable information could be transferred to third parties as one of our business assets.

### OTHER WEBSITES

The Site may contain links to other websites. Links from our Site to other sites or content are provided for your convenience only, and we do not have control over the content or privacy and security practices and policies of such third parties or other sites. Any personal information you provide on linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party’s privacy policy. We strongly recommend that you learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information. Similarly, some third parties may place cookies in advertisements and in other locations on the Site, and may place Web beacons on the Site in conjunction with such cookies. Information collected by these third parties is subject to those third parties’ policies governing use and disclosure of personal information.

When you are on the BitesizeBio’s Site, you may be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. We do not control the information collection and dissemination policies of third-party companies. These other site may independently collect data from or about you, solicit information from you, or place their own cookies on your computer. We are not responsible for any use of the information such third-party sites may collect.

For example, if you leave BitesizeBio and go to another site, Google, as a third party vendor, may use cookies to serve ads on your site.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by  
[visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

We partner with a limited number of third parties to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our websites. Advertising companies may use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to BitesizeBio in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be of interest to you. Learn more about this ‘behavioral advertising’ practice or opt-out of this use of your anonymous information at the National Advertising Initiative’s website:

<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

European Union users may visit [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) for more information and to opt out.

North America users please visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> to opt out of third party cookies.

You will not be targeted though you may still see adverts. Please note we are not responsible for the content of any third party websites.

### Your Information Choices

You can:

  * Review and edit your personal information through your BitesizeBio’s page
  * Control the messages you receive from BitesizeBio’ and other third parties
  * Tell us to close your account – you can always delete and close it yourself.

### CHILDREN

No information should be submitted to, or posted at, the Site by visitors under eighteen (18) years of age. Persons under eighteen (18) years of age are not permitted to access the Site and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from such individuals. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

### SECURITY

We use reasonable security measures in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and alteration of information while it is under our control. We cannot, however, guarantee the protection of information against interception, misappropriation, misuse or alteration, nor can we promise that your information may be not be disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others. Furthermore, we have no control over the security of other sites you might visit, interact with or do business with.

When you register for an account on the Site, we ask you to create a “username” and password. To protect the confidentiality of your personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of the Site by any person using your password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused or otherwise misappropriated.

### CHOICE

To opt-out of receiving marketing or other promotional communications from us, or to access, change or delete your personal information maintained by us, we provide you with the following options, you may:

(1) follow the “Unsubscribe” instructions contained in the communication from us;

(2) e-mail us at support@bitesizebio.com or

(3) write to us at the following address with your request:

BitesizeBio

Science Squared Ltd

Nine, Edinburgh BioQuarter

Little France Road,

Edinburgh EH16 4UX

### Your Acceptance of these Terms

By using this Site and/or Services, you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Site, Services and/or acceptance of our e-mail following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept these changes and agree to continue receiving e-mail from us. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please leave the website and do not continue to use it until you are accept the privacy policy and [Terms of Use](http://bitesizebio.com/terms-of-use/) of BitesizeBo.

Any disclosure of personal information will be strictly controlled in accordance with current UK legislation, in particular the UK Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act).

Our business changes constantly and our Privacy Policy may also change from time to time. You should check our website frequently to see recent changes, however, we will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of personal information collected in the past without your prior consent. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you.

For any inquiries you may contact us at:

BitesizeBio

Science Squared Ltd

Nine, Edinburgh BioQuarter

Little France Road,

Edinburgh EH16 4UX

### YOUR COMMENTS

We welcome your feedback. If you have any comments or concerns about this Policy or would like to contact us for any reason, you may reach us via e-mail at [support @ bitesizebio.com](mailto:support@bitesizebio.com).
